[Music]
meet raj mr backup
he has a plan a and plan b and a
contingency
you cannot blame him
life nowadays is fast and blurry
he is known as the man who thinks about
everything
but one day his wife fell in
nothing serious just a few tests and opd
visits and a few more tests
the bills piled up
his wife got tensed but raj like always
had thought of everything
for raj has secured his family with a
unique group health insurance policy
underwritten by icici lombard for icici
bank customers between 21 and 55 years
of age
it provides a comprehensive cover for
your and your family's health insurance
needs
what sets this plan apart is that it
offers one of the best opd covers of up
to rupees 25 000 per year
so your doctor visits diagnostic and
treatment expenses are well taken care
of
group health insurance provides a wide
option of some in short ranging from 5
black rupees to 25 lakh rupees
that can adequately meet the medical
exigencies for you and your loved ones
we have enhanced our health offerings by
increasing the coverage of corvid 19 not
only in case of hospitalization but also
in case of home health care
home health care treatment also covers
expenses for other ailments
other features include
24 hour hospitalization
day care procedure
air and road ambulance
donor expense
the health plans are now bigger and
better with reduced waiting periods
[Music]
what's more
raj can now manage all his insurance
needs with the help of the il take care
mobile app
whether it's registering and tracking
claims emergencies like ambulance
service
group health insurance your plan a b and
backup all in one
[Music]